const questions = [

  {
    question: "Bought bitcoin",
    answers: {a: "Yes", b: "I want to stay poor"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 5
  },

  {
    question: "Own bitcoin but never got KYCed",
    answers: { a: "No one but be know what I own", b: "I have nothing to hide"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 10
  },

  {
    question: "Moved bitcoin to a mobile wallet",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "I like my bitcoin on a third party"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 20
  },

  {
    question: "Moved bitcoin to a desktop wallet",
    answers: { a: "Full coin control", b: "Are the 'bitcoins' in the computer"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 10
  },

  {
    question: "Secured private keys",
    answers: { a: "No one but be know what I own", b: "I have nothing to hide"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 10
  },

  {
    question: "Recovered private keys",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "I like my bitcoin on a third party"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 20
  },

  {
    question: "Built segwit transactions",
    answers: { a: "Full coin control", b: "Are the 'bitcoins' in the computer"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 10
  },

  {
    question: "DCA bitcoin purchases (dollar cost average)",
    answers: { a: "Done", b: "Waiting for the price to go down"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 10
  },

  {
    question: "9. Replaced a transaction by fee",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 10
  },

  {
    question: "Sold all shitcoins",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 10
  },

  {
    question: "Never bought shitcoins",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 10
  },

  {
    question: "HODLing",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "Rather trade"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 1000
  },

  {
    question: "Built a bitcoin project in a bear market",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 100
  },

  {
    question: "Used a bitcoin ATM",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 100
  },

  {
    question: "Run a full validating node",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 1000
  },

  {
    question: "Run a lightning node",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 1000
  },

  {
    question: "sats the standard (unit of account)",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 100
  },

  {
    question: "Attended a bitcoin only meetup",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 100
  },

  {
    question: "Attended a bitcoin only conference",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 100
  },

  {
    question: "Constructed private keys on a hot wallet",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 100
  },

  {
    question: "Constructed private keys on a cold wallet",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 100
  },

  {
    question: "Recovered private keys on a cold wallet",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 100
  },

  {
    question: "Traded bitcoin on a decentralized exchange",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 1000
  },

  {
    question: "Built and signed multisig transactions",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 500
  },

  {
    question: "Earned bitcoin for services",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 1000
  },

  {
    question: "Earned bitcoin for bitcoin development",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 2000
  },

  {
    question: "Earned bitcoin for building bitcoin hardware",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 3000
  },

  {
    question: "Savings 90% converted to bitcoin ",
    answers: { a: "Irrisponsible long", b: "Fiat cautious"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 4000
  },

  {
    question: "Contributed code to the bitcoin protocol",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 5000
  },

  {
    question: "Mined bitcoin on a pool",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 6000
  },

  {
    question: "Solo mined bitcoin",
    answers: { a: "Yes", b: "No"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 7000
  },

  {
    question: "Solo mined bitcoin before the first halving",
    answers: { a: "CPU", b: "Mining is a waste of energy"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 8000
  },
  {
    question: "Mined the genesis block",
    answers: { a: "Bitcoin was my gift to ther world", b: "Mined it, but can't prove it"},
    correctAnswer: "a",
    points: 100001
  }

];
